About

Introduce yourself



Fresher ReactJS, Python Web

Nguyen Viet Xuan

丛 Oct 07, 1997 - ♂ Male

To apply my knowledge in the field of Javascript and Python programming into pratical use.

Looking forward to working in a professional environment.

To learn and to improve my professional experiences and other skills particularly of Javascript, backend Nodejs or Python.

What I Do



Web Design

Freelancer Python Django 1 year of experience.

Fresher ReactJS 2 months of practical experience.

Resume

Fresher

Education



2015-2020 University of Information Technology (UIT)

Information Security

Learn about malware analysis, system testing, Vulnerability Analysis, Firewalls, IDS/IPS system, etc.

Experience

JULY 2018 - SEP 2018 Certified Network Security Center (CNSC)

Interns

- Together with the lecturers research thesis topics
- There is the experience of the project using Django and Flask to write API

JULY 2018 - Now Thai Binh Engineering and Trading

IT Part-time

- Web application development with Django smartthuanviet.cf
- Website management
- It help desk

OCT 2019- DEC 2019 Beesight Soft

Fresher Reactjs

- Be involved in projects with Reactjs.

Skills

- Programming language: Javascript ,Python, C++, C#.
- Basic knowledge: Object Oriented Programming (OOP), Structured Query Language (SQL), HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Linux, Git.
- Framework: ReactJS, Django, Flask.
- Platform: Nodeis.
- Having knowledge of information security.
- Good teamwork skills.
- Quickly absorb new technologies.

Contact

Phone Numbers

0869 123 020 - 0797 07 10 97



Email

vietxuandev@gmail.com



Address

Dorm B, Vietnam national university Ho Chi Minh city, Di An, Binh Duong.



Facebook

fb.com/VietXuanDev



Instagram

instagram.com/vietxuandev



Website

http://vietxuandev.com